Howard Norton Cook Papers
Howard Norton Cook Papers
- Memorabilia
  - Printed material
    - Exhibition catalogs (miscellaneous non Cook) (by institution)
      - Denver Art Museum, 1947; 1956 (Box 18)
      - Los Angeles County Museum, 1951 (Box 18)
      - Metropolitan Museum of Art (New York, N.Y.), 1952 (Box 18)
      - Museum of Modern Art (New York, N.Y.), 1944 (Box 18)
      - Museum of New Mexico Art Gallery, 1951; 1953,; 1954,; 1960 (Box 18)
      - National Academy of Design, 1951; 1956 (Box 18)
      - Pennsylvania Academy of the Fine Arts, 1946 (Box 18)
      - Society of American Graphic Artists, 1945; 1956 (Box 18)
      - Whitney Museum of American Art, 1940s-1950s; 2 folders (Box 18)
      - Miscellaneous, A-Z (Box 18)
    - Periodicals
      - Bulletin - Section of Fine Arts, Public Buildings Administration, See United States. Public Buildings Administration. Bulletin.
      - Bulletin - Treasury Department Art Projects, See Correspondence Subject Files: United States. Treasury Department Art Projects. Bulletin.
      - Carnegie Magazine, Dec. 1947; Dec. 1948;; Dec. 1951 (Box 19)
      - Claremont College Bulletin Institute of Art (H. Cook, instructor), Mar. 1951 (Box 19)
      - Common Ground, Spring 1941; Spring 1942 (Box 19)
      - Philadelphia Museum Bulletin; Handbook numbers (2), May 1944 (Box 19)
      - Print Collectors' Chronicle v. 1, no. 4 (Box 19)
    - Reports
      - Archaeological Institute of America. School of American Research, 1954 (Box 19)
      - Art Students League, 1964-1965 (Box 19)
      - John Simon Guggenheim Memorial Foundation, 1937-1946; 1959-1960; 3 folders (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 items (Box 19)
  - Miscellany, 7 items (Box 19)